让我走 麦克
Let me fucking go, Mike!
楼上有一间空房
We have a spare room upstairs.
没必要把她的麻烦变成我们的麻烦
We don't need her trouble becomin' our trouble.
是谁下的命令
Who ordered this?
没人组织 伙计 这就是问题所在
Nobody, man. That's the fuckin' problem.
里面没有领头人 麦克
There's no leaders inside, Mike.
整个监狱 就没个能管事的人
Not one shot caller in the whole goddamn camp.
消息进不去也出不来
We can't get no messages in or out.
我有主意了
I have an idea.
这一次你必须要相信我 因为过程会有些痛
And you're gonna have to trust me, 'cause it's gonna sting.
她不见了
She's gone.
不见了
Gone?
要是我能把四个帮派的头目都给你弄来呢
What if I can get you the leaders of all four gangs?
也就是正在交战的所有人
Everyone that's at war.
他们要把我们关多久
How long they planning on holding us?
你们要多久才能
How long is it gonna take you
把里面的帮派调教好
to get your house together inside?
-不会太久  -这招太狠了 麦克
- Not long. - Ice cold, Mike.
你想个好招
Name another way.
囚犯运输
我没有家
I have no home.
这就是你家
You are home.
你就是麦克
Are you Mike?
是我
I am.
你跟坎迪斯聊了吗
Did you speak to Candace?
聊了
I did.
她跟你说只有我一个
She told you it was just me.
对
She did.
我不会对你撒谎的
I wouldn't lie to you.
我知道
I know.
我以前在兰辛市的酒店工作过
I worked some hotels in Lansing.
我只是需要点时间
I just needed some time, you know?
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead,
在暴乱的时候 所以
in the riot, so...
我那时不知道该去哪里
I didn't know where to go.
不找麦克吗
No Mike?
操他的麦克
Fuck Mike.
你操了吗
Did you?
什么
What?
没有
No.
我相信你 艾丽丝
I believe you, Iris.
我要睡了 我累了
I'm going to sleep, I'm tired.
明天的事明天再说吧
We can deal with tomorrow when tomorrow's here.
NEW字幕组翻译
翻译  鹅蔼玲
翻译  千阳
翻译  江湖
翻译  炭炭
翻译  Melody
校对  头上长仙草
校对  千阳
时间轴  长颂
时间轴  斤日
时间轴  江湖
时间轴  konosjda
时间轴  扎啤花生米
啦啦队  千阳
总监  千阳
CSEG克隆字幕提取组
提取  Caliro
@CSEG克隆字幕提取组
默丘利快递服务
本字幕由CSEG克隆字幕提取组提取分享  仅供学习交流之用  禁止压制  禁止删除字幕组及CSEG署名
你走吧
Go on.
全部趴下
Get the fuck on the ground!
趴下 趴下
Get down, lay down!
把枪口从我脸上拿开 小子
Get that gun out of my face, boy.
我老胳膊老腿可没办法给人跪下
I'm too damn old to be gettin' on my knees for anybody.
里面的混蛋 最好别摔了我的东西
Fuckers in there, they'd better not break my shit!
武器放下 史蒂夫 给她拿张椅子
Lower the weapons! Stevie, can we get her a chair?
你知道我孙子是谁吧
You know who my grandson is.
我知道 夫人 这是我们来的原因
I do, ma'am, yes. That's why we're here.
我知道您照料孩子挺忙的
I know you got your hands full with the kids.
我们速战速决 我保证
We'll be in and out real quick, I promise.
操
Fuck me.
靠
Oh, boy.
你把她安置到你妈家里去了
You put her at your mom's!
对啊
Yeah!
-确实是  -然后她就...
- I did. - And she just...
跑了
ran away.
对 我不是说了嘛
Yeah, like I fuckin' said!
而且你也不知道她去哪了
And you have no idea where she went.
对 不知道
No. No idea.
所以 看起来我们两个
So, it appears that neither one of us
都不知道该怎么照顾她 对吧
know how to look after her. Right?
所以我要去干活了
So I'm gonna go to work.
你滚去爱干啥干啥吧
You can fuck off and do whatever you do.
喂 你可是联邦线人啊
Hey, you're a federal informant.
-你闭嘴行吗  -我们付钱让你提供消息
- Can you fuckin' save it? - We pay you to inform.
好 我的消息是我屁都不知道
Okay, I'll inform you I don't know fuckin' shit!
如果麦洛·森特逃狱了 他会找到她的
If Milo Sunter's out there, he will find her.
你忙你的去吧 好吗 我也去做我的事
Do what you gotta do, okay? I'll do what I do.
还有 我告诉你
And I'll tell you this...
如果你逼她作证
If you forced her to testify...
他就会杀了她 这对谁有好处呢
he will kill her, and who fuckin' wins then?
操
Fuck.
我怎么了吗
What did I do?
要喝咖啡吗
You want some coffee?
要 好的
Yeah, yeah.
很好 咖啡很好
That'd be great. Love some coffee.
谢谢
Appreciate it.
怎么了 到底怎么了
Yeah? What, what?
我相信那个女孩经历过地狱般的折磨
I don't doubt what hell that girl's been though,
但你没必要也一起受折磨
but it's not yours to live in.
听着 丽贝卡 我没想一起受折磨好吗
Look, Rebecca, I'm not tryin' to live in that shit, okay?
我只是想把她解脱出来
I'm just tryin' to get her the fuck out of it.
你气色真好 还有早安之类的屁话
You look lovely, good morning, and all that bullshit!
谢谢你
Thank you!
喂
Yeah?
什么
What?
什么时候
When?
你他妈在逗我吧
You're fucking kidding me!
停车场内禁止骑车 滑板 溜冰 玩耍
搞什么
What in the fuck?
你是左耳进右耳出吗
Do you listen to anything I say?!
看看这是哪 你冷静一点
Look where you are. You gotta keep it down.
金斯敦警局
你们他妈的突袭民宅
You fuckin' raided the Commons!
线人告诉我们那里有非法毒品活动
Hey, CI told us that there was illegal drug activity.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?!
那地方什么时候没有毒品活动
When is there not fuckin' drug activity?!
动动你们的猪脑子吧
Use your fuckin' heads, you guys!
我的老天爷
Jesus Christ!
我跟他们谈好了
I negotiated the deal!
领头人在里面时你们不要动手
You don't attack them while the leaders are inside!
邦尼为我们付出了代价
Bunny takes a hit for us.
-你们在搞什么  -付出了代价 麦克
- What the fuck?! - Takes a hit, Mike!
他是个毒贩子
He is a drug dealer.
只凭他是你的毒贩子...
Just 'cause he's your fuckin' drug dealer...
我都不知道该怎么跟你说
I don't know what to tell ya.
他在里面 替我们办事
He's inside, working for us.
别把这事忘了 白痴
Let's not forget that, fuck heads.
你要是非得把他外婆家的门给踹了
He's not gonna do fuckin' shit all for us
他什么屁事
if you're goin' down and bustin' down
-都不会替我们办  -麦克
- his grandma's fuckin' door! - Mikey...
我们非常有他妈的礼貌
We were fuckin' super fuckin' respectful.
-特别有礼貌  -很有礼貌
- Very respectful. - Very respectful.
而且我非常注意了
I took it fuckin' easy!
你们这群白痴 这搞不好会搅起外面的冲突
You dipshits, this'll start a war out here.
这是你们想要的吗
Is that what you want?
你想我们啥也不干
You want us to stop bein' police?
这是你想要的吗
Is that what you want?
去他们的
Fuck them!
-去他们的  -去他们的
- Fuck them? - Fuck them.
-去你的  -去他们的
- Fuck you. - Fuck them.
我们就快把这事搞定了 好吗
We're this fuckin' close to getting it done, okay?
去他们的
Fuck them, okay? Fuck them.
-去他们的  -嘿 嘿
- Fuck them! - Hey, hey.
操...都他妈冷静点
Fuckin'... calm the fuck down.
就差这一点了
We're this close.
麦克 我们才是一条船上的人
Mike, we're on the same goddamn team.
是啊 你们真他妈会给我的工作添堵
Yeah, you're makin' my job fuckin' harder.
我不是给你们擦屁股的 混蛋
I'm not your fuckin' janitor, you cunt!
去你的
Fuck you!
这狗地方真他妈的热 操
It's hot as a motherfucker in this bitch, man, shit.
太阳才刚出来 邦
Sun's barely up, Bun.
你要把体内毒素给流干了啊
You gon' sweat out all your toxins.
出自《圣经》 常用来表达"身体发肤受之'上帝'"之意
我的身体是圣殿什么的 是吧
Yeah, my body's a temple and all that shit, right?
邦尼·华盛顿
Bunny Washington!
去他妈的 兄弟
Fuck that cracker, bruh.
不用听他的话
You ain't here to answer to his shit.
那个崽子是麦克的人
That motherfucker one of Mike's boys.
他八成是有什么指示
He probably got some instructions or some shit.
你不需要什么指示来教你怎么管这破地方
You don't need no instructions on how to run this shit.
要我看 麦克就是最不应该
The way I see it, Mike is the last fuckin' dude
发号施令的混蛋
that should be givin' instructions.
一开始就是他的破事把事情弄成这样
His shit is what got shit twisted in the first place.
嘿 听着
Listen.
从现在起 我们要相信麦克有计划
From now on, we gonna trust that Mike got a plan
把这事摆平
to make this shit right.
把这里收拾干净 我们拿回监狱
All this shit shake out, and we get our pound.
他妈的动起来
Let's fucking go!
如果他的法子不行
If it don't go his way...
就按照我们的法子来
We run it like we do.
邦尼·华盛顿 我没时间跟你耗
Bunny Washington! I ain't got all day!
这王八羔子叫老子名字 好像老子欠他钱一样
This motherfucker screamin' my name like I owe him money.
嘿
Hey.
介意把他手铐摘了吗
Wanna take this shit off him?
你不会想这么做的
You don't wanna do that.
他说的对 你不会想这么做的
Man's right. You don't wanna do that.
-邦尼  -嗯哼
- Bunny... - Mm-hmm?
尽快放我出去 麦克
Let me out, Mike.
我正在努力 好吗
I'm workin' on it, okay?
你把里面的烂摊子收拾完 我把外面的收拾完
Get your shit settled in here, I'll settle mine outside.
收拾烂摊子
Shit is settled.
麦克 烂摊子永远都收拾不完
Shit is never gettin' settled, Mike.
我只不过是修修补补 兄弟
I'm just fingerin' dykes in here, bruh.
我在这里面整顿秩序 对吗
I'm in here linin' it out, right?
帮你办事
Doin' your shit.
我要保证
I want assurances.
我他妈正在努力
I'm fuckin' workin' on it.
你的话在我这已经没任何信用了
Your word don't mean shit to me no more.
我不想听你说你还在努力
I don't wanna hear working.
我下周会从助理检察官那里弄到进展
I'm gonna get something from the assistant DA next week.
行吗
Okay?
听我说
Listen to me.
你还需要什么来把这事处理好
What do you need in here to make things right?
有些刺头需要拔掉
Some chips gotta get knocked off.
我出去之后 由我表弟掌事
My cousin will run point when I get out.
好 你还要我做什么
Yeah, what do you need from me?
看守暂时回避 明天五点
Backs turned, 5 o'clock tomorrow.
行
Fine.
你去看我地盘没
You check in on mine?
禁止囚犯越过此处
手机店重新营业了
Cell phone shop is up and running.
我的人呢
My people?
有人照顾
They're taken care of.
操 兄弟 你这次这么搞
Shit, bruh, you do a motherfucker like this...
得花很长时间修复关系了 麦克
it's gonna take a long-ass time to bury this hatchet, Mike.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
搞快点 把事情搞定 行吗
Keep it tight, get it done. Okay?
五点回避五分钟 行吗
Five at five. Okay?
明天
Tomorrow.
-我可以做到  -好
- I can do that. - Yeah.
卡里姆呢
Kareem?
别让他知道 他现在是管理层
Keep him insulated. He's the management now.
禁止进入
清理石棉中
什么情况
What the fuck?
天哪
Jesus Christ.
见到你真好
Fuckin' good to see ya.
-见到你真好  -见到你真好
- Hey, good to see you! - Good to see you!
你们终于被流放了啊
Finally banished you fuckers, huh?
你愿意进来了啊
You decided to come in?
-嗯 嗯  -见到你真高兴
- Well, well, huh? - Nice to see ya.
怎么样啊
- How you doin', huh? - Yeah.
我还行 还行
I'm all right. I'm all right.
-好啊  -谢谢
- Good! - Hey, thank you.
-我能跟你聊几句吗  -好啊
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yeah.
史蒂夫 让这些家伙滚回去工作
Stevie, just get these fuckers back to work.
快乐时光结束了 大伙们
Happy time's over, people.
-就这样  -没错 就这样
- That's it? - Yep, that's it.
就这样
That's it.
-见到你真高兴  -我也是
- It's good to see you. - Yeah, you too.
你想喝点啥 咖啡 要吃甜甜圈吗
Well, what do you want? A coffee, you want a doughnut?
-你要...  -不 不 不用 我不饿
- You want...? - Nah, nah, I'm good, I'm good.
我就来...
I just...
我就待一会
You know, I just need a minute.
要么锁好 要么被盗
操 回来的感觉真好
Fuck, it's good to be back here.
见到你真好
It's fuckin' great to see you.
我也是
You too, man.
你还好吗
You're good?
那群混蛋给我停职了
Fuckers suspended me.
让我等待调查
Pending the investigation.
停薪 而且...
No pay, and...
他们清楚我孩子快出生了 我直接说
It's like, they know I got a kid on the way, and I said,
"去你妈的 我不干了"
"Fuck you motherfuckers. I quit."
你做得对 去他妈的
You did the right thing. Fuck them.
你要回这上班
You need to be here.
我们需要更多人手上街巡逻
We need more fuckin' soldiers on the street.
我也有此意
That's what I want.
我说 我们要怎么办才能让我回来
I mean, what do we gotta do to make that happen?
你得有点耐心
You gotta fuckin' be patient.
-我...  -在州警局认为你开枪是正当的之前
They're not gonna put you back on the street
他们是不会让你上街巡逻的
until the staties call this a righteous fuckin' shoot.
我开枪真是正当的
It fuckin' was a righteous shoot!
这就是官僚主义的狗屎作风
Fuckin' bureaucratic bullshit.
但是
But...
你只能低头忍受着
you gotta fuckin' keep your head down.
直到内务部的报告证明你的清白
Until the IA report comes back clean.
等报告一出 你的前途又是一片光明了
Once that happens, you're fuckin' golden.
我在这快活不下去了 老兄
I'm dyin' in here, man. It's...
这可是我的家乡啊 你懂吗
This is home for me. You know?
你会跟别人倾诉吗
You talkin' to anybody?
你他妈的会跟别人倾诉吗
Are you fuckin' talkin' to anybody?
我只有一间空荡的公寓
I got a fuckin' empty apartment,
还有一只前女友留下的猫
I got a fuckin' ex-girlfriend's cat.
它们都不会跟我聊天的 好吧
Neither one of 'em will talk to me, all right?
你有值得奋斗的动力
You got fuckin' shit to work for.
有一个爱你的老婆
You have got a fuckin' wife who loves you.
还有个即将出生的孩子
You have got a kid on the way.
我不需要心理医生 伊恩 我需要一份工作
I don't need a shrink, Ian. I need a job.
兄弟 我理解你 好吗
Brother, I got you. All right?
-好的  -别担心好吗
- All right. - All right?
-好的  -我理解你
- All right. - I got ya.
-我知道  -振作点好吧
- I know. - All right?
好的
Okay.
内务部证明我清白前 金斯敦警局不会让我回来
KPD can't take me back until IA clears me,
我可能要等几个月的时间
and that's probably gonna take a couple months.
但问题是 我等不了几个月 麦克
And it's like, I don't have a fuckin' couple months, Mike.
我需要工作 老哥 我得赚钱
I need somethin', man. I, I, I gotta fuckin' earn.
为什么不趁机休息一下呢 对吧
Well, why don't you just take a fuckin' break, right?
暂时不管这些烂事
Put a pause on this shit.
我要是休息了 就会胡思乱想
I take a break, I'm gonna fucking lose it.
我得保持忙碌 我现在已经有点疯了
I gotta stay busy. I'm already losin' it.
为什么不从身边小事开始呢
You know, why don't you do shit around here?
帮老妈干点活 对吧
Help Ma out, right?
修修房门栅栏门 剪剪草坪
Fix the doors, the gates, mow the lawn,
做点家务 对吧
that kinda shit, right?
滚蛋 别这么敷衍我
Fuck you, don't brush me off like that.
好吧 听着 要是你想干点杂活
All right, look, if you want a chore,
我就分你一件杂活
I can give you a chore.
好啊 正合我意 你想让我干什么
Yes, that's what I want. What you got?
检查火车站 公共汽车站和出租车
Check the train station, bus depot, taxis.
每一处都要查
All that.
老妈给过她一份庇护所清单 也去查一下
Ma gave her a list of shelters, check those.
还没找到艾丽丝
Can't find Iris?
没有
Nope.
麦克
Oh, Mike...
你得把情况告诉联邦调查局或者金斯敦警局之类的
You gotta give that to the feds, or somethin', to KPD.
我这么说吧
'Cause I tell you what,
她可能已经回纽约 或者到别的地方
she's probably back in New York or wherever the fuck,
去享受她自己的美好生活了
livin' her best fuckin' life.
最好的情况就是
Best case scenario,
她远远地离开了金斯敦
she's put miles between Kingstown and herself.
因为要是她还在这
'Cause if she's still here...
好了 这也是我要搞清楚的事
Well, that's what I'm tryin' to find out.
行吧
Okay?
贝尔维特路
有人吗
Knock, knock.
让他过来
Let him in.
你想干什么 麦克
What do you want, Mike?
就是来看看你
Just checkin' in on you.
看你是不是安好
Makin' sure you're okay.
你跟他聊过了吗
You talk to him yet?
谁
Who?
他不在里面 所以...
He wasn't identified on the inside, so...
-你懂吧  -懂了
- Oh... - Yeah.
尸体真的很多啊
A lot of bodies.
别废话了 约瑟夫 行吗
Oh, cut the shit, Joseph. Come on.
你和我都清楚他越狱了
You and I both know that he's out.
我很乐意见到我的朋友重归自由
I would love to see my friend free.
真的吗 他是你的朋友
Is that right, your friend?
麦洛看重忠诚
Milo values loyalty.
而我最忠诚了
And I am loyal above all.
是啊 九年了 你一直是他的跟班
Well, nine years... You're his errand boy.
没有什么是你能做到而他不能的 是吧
Nothin' you can do now that he can't. Right?
是有小孩在这吗
Is that a fuckin' baby?
我什么也没听见
I hear nothing.
没有吗
No?
你到底想干什么 麦克
What do you want, Mike?
你们把她怎么样了
What'd you do with her?
谁
Who?
你们把她杀了吗
Did you kill her?
麦克 当妓女向联邦探员告密时
Mike, when whore talks to feds...
你觉得会发生什么
What do you think happens?
别过来
Stop.
快出去 帕什拉·冯
Get out. Pashla von!
我还会回来的
I'll be back.
你给我等着吧
You can count on it.
告诉我你已经有进展了
Tell me you got some movement.
嗨 麦克
Hey, Mike!
我很好 你怎么样
I'm fine, how are you?
告诉我点进展就行 伊芙琳 说吧
Just give me somethin', Evelyn. Come on.
我正在说服上司
I'm workin' the boss,
据我所知 一切顺利
everything's good as far as I know.
对我来说这没什么帮助
Well, that doesn't really fucking help me.
我跟他们承诺过 我需要确切的出狱日期
You know, I made promises. I need release dates.
或许这件事可以先不着急
Well, maybe you shouldn't have done that.
还有很多文件要提交
A lot of paper to be pushed.
听着 我得带你去看些东西
Listen, I need you to see something.
现在吗
Right now?
30分钟后
30 minutes.
我们在沃里克拘留所见
Meet me at Warwick Detention.
去不了 我还有烂摊子要收拾
I can't. I got, I got shit to do.
这是特意为你准备的
Hey, this is for you.
这个世界正在改变 你得好好看看了
The world is changing, and you need to see it.
行吧 行吧 我去
Fine, I'm comin'. Fine.
出去
Get out.
结束了吗
Are you finished?
不好意思
Ya tol'ko nachal.
我这人干活只看结果 不看效率
Mne platiat ne za skorost', a za zdelannuiu rabotu.
先麻醉一下
To numb the area.
不要动
Hold still, please.
这里就是你的新家
This is your new home.
你有床 保险箱 衣柜
You have a bed, safe, closet.
你一晚上能挣五千
You will make $5,000 a night.
如果能挣到八千 皆大欢喜
If you make eight, good for you.
可是只有四千 我们就要算账了
If you make four, we have a problem.
沃里克拘留所
Warwick Detention is
是金斯敦唯一一座私人监狱
the sole private penial institution in Kingstown.
沃里克集团从2018年开始运营
Warwick Group has run it since 2018,
它也是在暴动期间 唯一一座没有出现暴力事件的监狱
and it is the only prison that saw no violence during the riot.
没有放风时间 没有教育服务 没有食堂
It's easy to see no violence when you have no yard time,
没有小卖部 确实很难有暴力冲突啊
no education service, no cafeteria, no commissary...
怎么感觉你说的是帐篷城呢 莫尔先生
Sounds like you're describing Tent City, Mr. Moore.
那边的"无暴力"情况怎么样呢
How's that no violence workin' out?
特殊时期
It's a unique situation.
好吧 在接下来的三年里
Well, in the next three years,
金斯敦将进行修缮和改造
Kingstown will be repaired and retrofitted.
接下来的五年里 金斯敦的每一座监狱
In the next five years, every prison in Kingstown
都将和沃里克集团签约
will be contracted to the Warwick Group.
她简直痴心妄想 这根本不可能
She's out of her fuckin' mind. That'll never happen.
都在慢慢改变 麦克 所以我才想让你来
It is happening, Mike. That's why I wanted you to come.
兰辛市[密歇根州首府]那帮人还在讨论吧
They're still debating in Lansing.
不是吗
Right?
有关暴动的结果报告还没出来
Report on the riot's not even out.
沃里克在做报告 你应该了解他们一下
Warwick's doing the report. You should get to know them.
是不是逛得有些无聊了
Are we boring you back there?
没有 很棒 太他妈有趣了
No, it's great. Fuckin' interesting.
帐篷城只是临时措施
Tent City is temporary.
沃里克才是一劳永逸的解决方案
And Warwick is a permanent solution.
所以 下周我们会带
So we're gonna bring some of your inmates
你们的部分囚犯去到锚湾
to Anchor Bay in the next week,
其余的人就安排他们来这里
and the rest of the overflow will come here.
你考虑得很充分了
You're overbooked already.
我们知道如何关押囚犯
Well, we know how to warehouse.
我们在其它州 其它城市也有机构...
We have facilities in other counties, other states...
她怎么跟个房产中介一样
She's like a fuckin' real estate agent.
出口
简直他妈的离谱 看看这群人
This is fuckin' ridiculous. Look at these guys.
还以为是在游猎探险呢
Look like they're on fuckin' safari.
真操蛋
Fuck me.
回来第一天还有点意思 对吧
First day back is fun, yeah?
就像骑自行车一样 但至少报酬还不错
Like riding a bicycle, but the pay's better.
我是塔蒂
I'm Tati.
如果你和其他姑娘有矛盾
You have a problem with the other girls,
可以来找我
you come to me.
有任何需要...
You need anything...
都可以跟我说
Let me know.
你已经做得很好了
You did good already.
之后会越来越好
You're going to do fine.
宝贝
Baby.
麦洛会来吗
Does Milo come by?
谁
Who?
有必要装不认识吗
We're gonna do this?
不会来
He does not.
那我能去找他吗
Well, can I go to him?
只有他找你的份儿
When he calls.
你应该肩负重任吧 塔蒂
You got shit on you, Tati?
什么重任
What kinda shit?
他妈的给我们洗脑 即便今天过得凄惨
The kinda shit that makes today feel like
明天还是充满希望的一天
I'm hopin' tomorrow might.
有希望是好的
Hope is good.
希望没了 人也死了
Hope dies, we die.
对
Yeah.
有多糟
How bad?
现在才跟我说
And you're tellin' me now?
行吧 我这就去
Fine, I'm on my way.
坏消息吗
Bad news?
我认识你吗
I know you?
我知道她在哪里
I know where she is.
她有麻烦了
She's in trouble.
她不好好表现 就会受到惩罚
She won't perform, and she'll be punished for it,
表现好了 也不过是折磨自己
or she'll perform to punish herself.
她跟麦洛在一起吗
She with Milo?
麦洛死了 我猜
Milo's dead, I think.
你们的人把他杀了
Your people killed him.
聊得挺投缘 我先忙去了
Good talkin' to you. I got shit to do.
你还想继续当超人去救她吗
You wanna put on a cape and save this girl,
我可以给你留扇门
I can leave a door open for you.
在俱乐部的巷子里
In the alley at the club.
出口
你在找什么呢 麦克
What are you looking for, Mike?
你知道我要找的东西可不少 约瑟夫
You know I'm lookin' for a lot of things, Joseph.
但有些事情咱们日后再说
And let's just save that shit for another day.
-你说什么  -你可能没有日后了
- What do you say? - You might not have another day.
你要找的人不在这里
None of what you're looking for is here.
你女朋友可能胳膊上正扎着针
Your girlfriend is probably dead by a dumpster
横死在垃圾箱旁边了
with a fucking needle hanging out of her arm.
或者是在某个有钱人的床上
Or in a rich man's bed.
那位是你的情人吗
That your baby?
她是谁不关你的事
That baby is none of your fucking business.
确实你也不会让你妈来帮你
Then maybe you don't want to send the mother
干这种活儿
to do your damn job.
麦洛知道你回来了吗
Does Milo know that you're back on the town?
你可真有意思 麦克
You're a funny guy, Mike.
滚开 把枪放下
Fuck off, put it down.
跟你们老板说一声 我知道他已经跑了...
Tell your fuckin' boss that I know he's out...
我会找到他的
And I'm gonna find him.
别瞎费劲了 一帮混蛋
Don't bother! Fuckin' assholes.
咱俩今天能当好兄弟吗
We gon' be brothers today?
不能
No.
他在哪
Hey, where is he?
妈呀 你丫这是怎么了
Jesus, what the fuck happened to you?
我真他妈的 邦尼
Jesus fuckin' Christ, Bunny.
看来计划进行的很顺利哈
Looks like the plan's workin', huh?
我可没有幽默感 麦克 没有...
I got no humor, Mike. Not...
一丁点都没有
Not a fuckin' lick.
你以为能瞒得住我吗
You thought I wasn't gon' hear?
他们突击搜查我家 恐吓我的家人
They raid my home, they terrorize my family,
你竟然没告诉我
and you don't tell me.
我当时不知道 邦尼
I didn't know about it, Bunny.
鬼才信你不知道 麦克
Fuck you didn't know, Mike?
你必须得知道 因为你需要我
You need to know. You needed me.
你怂到有话不敢直说
You too chicken shit to talk straight.
我还以为我们关系已经够铁了
I thought we was past that.
别扯到友情 好吧
Let's not make this about friends, all right?
我们不是朋友
We're not friends.
你他妈真说对了
Yeah, that's for damn sure.
事情会变得很糟糕 麦克
This will break down, Mike.
可能再也回不去了
Might not be no comin' back from this shit.
他妈的赶紧给我弄出去
Get me the fuck outta here,
不然小心我报复你们
or there's gonna be some payback.
我并不是指监狱里的狱警
And no, I don't mean no fuckin' guards on the inside.
或者街上那帮警察
Or them cops on the street. Nuh-uh, nuh-uh.
我要以牙还牙搞你们的家人
This shit's gonna hit close to home.
好了 拜托 别做得那么绝
All right, come on. Let's not go there.
你已经把事情做绝了 麦克
You already fuckin' did, Mike.
你要明白那不关我事
You have to understand this is not me.
是他妈的金斯敦警局
It was fucking KPD.
要你有啥用 麦克
What good are you, Mike?
你连自己人都控制不了
You can't even control your own people.
不该发生这事的 你明白吗
This wasn't supposed to happen, you understand me?
我该做的都做到了 好吧
I done my piece. All right?
限你48小时内把我放出去
You got 48 hours. Get my ass back on the street.
我正在努力
I'm workin' on mine.
你知道我今天小命差点没了吗
You know my shit damn near fucking ended today?
赶紧他妈的给我放出去 麦克
Get me the fuck outta here, Mike.
我会的
I'll make it happen.
你保护不了我
You can't protect me.
和我的人
My people, nah.
我得靠自己
So I gotta do it.
他妈的给我放出去
Get me the fuck outta here.
你欠我的
You owe me that.
这是你他妈欠我的 麦克
You fucking owe me, Mike.
谁都不许动邦尼一根汗毛
Nobody touches fucking Bunny.
我要你把这当成个人使命
Okay, I want you to make it your personal fuckin' mission.
他可是这监狱里最狠的混蛋 麦克
He is the biggest swingin' dick on this yard, Mike.
他是自己人 而且履行了承诺
He's an ally and he made good on his end.
从现在起 要是他发生任何意外
Okay, so whatever the fuck happens to him now...
你也得遭殃
happens to you.
明白吗
Understand?
他要是受伤 你也会受伤
He gets hurt, you're gonna get hurt.
他如果流血 你也会流血
He bleeds, you bleed.
明白
Yeah.
真他妈的... 操
This motherfuckin'...
《金斯敦市长》下集预告
Next time on Mayor of Kingstown...
你跟邦尼·华盛顿和其他
You made deals with Bunny Washington
黑帮老大做了约定
and the other generals.
以我之名做的约定
Deals with my name in your fucking mouth.
他们在转移囚犯 麦克
They movin' people, Mike.
我绝对会给你弄出来
I'm getting you the fuck out.
我保证
You have my word.
你已经风光不再了
You're losin' your fucking mojo!
有位女士说她丈夫在工地里挖出来
Lady said her husband dug up a box of these
一箱子这个
at his worksite.
你只是刚好找到了这个
You just found this?
麦洛会来找回属于他的东西
Milo's gonna come lookin' for what's his.
你会成为我们组织里的麻烦吗 艾丽丝
Are you gonna be a problem in our clan, Iris?
你是想把整个房子烧掉
You're lookin' to burn this whole house down.
叫你小弟做好丫分内的事
Tell your boy to do his fuckin' job.
他们会来找你的
They comin' for you.
这笔帐迟早要加倍奉还
There's gonna be some payback.